<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Custom_spinner</string>


    <string-array name="title">
        <item>Select</item>
        <item>Android</item>
        <item>Java</item>
        <item>Oracle</item>
        <item>Facebook</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="desc_short">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Android is a mobile operating system currently developed by Google</item>
        <item>Java is a set of computer software and specifications
                  developed by Sun Microsystems</item>
        <item>The Oracle Corporation is an American global computer
             technology corporation, headquartered in Redwood City, California.</item>
        <item>Facebook is a corporation and online social networking
          service headquartered in Menlo Park, California, in the United States</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="desc_long">
        <item> </item>
        <item>Android is a mobile operating system (OS) currently developed
       by Google, based on the Linux kernel and designed primarily for touchscreen
       mobile devices such as smartphones and tablets. Android\'s user interface is
       mainly based on direct manipulation, using touch gestures that loosely correspond
       to real-world actions, such as swiping, tapping and pinching, to manipulate on-screen
       objects, along with a virtual keyboard for text input. In addition to touchscreen
       devices, Google has further developed Android TV for televisions, Android Auto for cars,
        and Android Wear for wrist watches, each with a specialized user interface.
      Variants of Android are also used on notebooks, game consoles, digital cameras,
       and other electronics.</item>
        <item>Java is a set of computer software and specifications developed by
       Sun Microsystems, later acquired by Oracle Corporation, that provides a
     system for developing application software and deploying it in a cross-platform
     computing environment. Java is used in a wide variety of computing platforms
     from embedded devices and mobile phones to enterprise servers and supercomputers.
     While less common, Java applets run in secure, sandboxed environments to provide
     many features of native applications and can be embedded in HTML pages.</item>
        <item>The Oracle Corporation is an American global computer technology corporation,
     headquartered in Redwood City, California. The company primarily specializes in
     developing and marketing database software and technology, cloud engineered systems
     and enterprise software products – particularly its own brands of database management
     systems. In 2011 Oracle was the second-largest software maker by revenue, after Microsoft.
    The company also develops and builds tools for database development and systems of
   middle-tier software, enterprise resource planning (ERP) software, customer relationship
    management (CRM) software and supply chain management (SCM) software.</item>
        <item>Facebook is a corporation and online social networking service
     headquartered in Menlo Park, California, in the United States. Its website
    was launched on February 4, 2004, by Mark Zuckerberg with his Harvard College roommates
   and fellow students Eduardo Saverin, Andrew McCollum, Dustin Moskovitz and Chris Hughes.
    The founders had initially limited the website\'s membership to Harvard students,
    but later expanded it to colleges in the Boston area, the Ivy League, and Stanford
   University. It gradually added support for students at various other universities and
    later to high-school students.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>
